(THE YARNS)
I got confirmation from the forensic lab results.
The murderer is that girl's identical twin.
Release this kid's photo to press,
set a reward of five million baht for the capture,
Father, Sky is in a lot of trouble because of your actions.
You used the people as an excuse.
Fah
Fah, you come back to mommy.
Just a little bit more,
and I will be able to avenge you, my mother.
If that day comes, I will let you kill that
damn beast with your own hands.
Yes, the song is the key.
So now we are left with the tenth victim.
We need to get the list from Mr. Pakin
and compare it with the occupation like last time.
Hey, are you a star? Why don't I know you?
Hey, Sergeant! This person is very famous.
He's famous all the way to China.
He has a lot of fans.
Are you kidding?
If he's that famous, why don't I know him?
He's famous among BL fans.
Oh, I see. BL actors.
Do you watch BL series too?
My sister is his fan.
Found it.
What did you find, sister?
You sounded like you won the lottery.
Gratitude.
The mysterious grateful person might mean...
'Famous teen star, Tali Tanuwat,
won 2022 Best Son Award.'
Sergeant,
contact this person to me as soon as possible.
Yes, sir.
What?
Do you want me to be a murderer's bait?
I don't want to.
I may seem selfish, but I think it's too risky.
That's right, officer.
Why does it have to be Tali?
Because the police expected that
your child may be the murderer's next target.
Here it is. It is just a maybe, meaning it's not certain.
That riddle you mention,
it could be somebody else too.
I don't want to do that.
I assure you that we will protect you well. You will be safe.
If you make a mistake...
and something really happens,
who will be responsible for my family?
Anyhow,
I'm really sorry, but I can't help you.
- Let's go back, Mom.
- Okay, dear.
Wait a minute.
I want you to look at this first.
What is this?
Scientific criminal forgery of population
registration documents.
Simply put,
You have killer genes.
I have a killer gene?
No way.
I am an actor,
behave well,
and I work for charity.
There's no way I have killer genes.
You might not know.
But your genes are tampered
with from the moment you are born.
Is it true, mom?
This is not a threat.
I just want to inform you that
you are guilty of gene tampering.
What if Tali agrees to help you?
You won't press charges against Tali for this, will you?
Can you assure me that
my son won't be harmed in any way.
Mom,
I have already installed the tracking device
on your mobile phone.
Is that all?
Not yet.
Please take off your shirt.
Huh?
We need to install a tracking device on you
for safety.
- Please come.
- Yes, sir.
Stand up, please.
Do you notice this red light?
If the red light is flashing,
it means you are in the sight of the police.
You will be safe.
Is this really working, Lan?
Why do you make the team
keep distant from Tali that much?
If you follow too closely, the culprit will become aware and change their target.
It's like the last time when the murderer
changed the target and killed Mr. Pakin instead.
Then how will we know when they're attacking?
Sky
What does Sky see?
Sky saw Dr. Anya.
Not what Skye sees
- What do you see in here, Sky?
- That person will die.
Sky, look at me.
What do you see in here?
Yes.
Dr. Anya is right.
- I see it here. I see it here.
- In here,
who do you see, Sky?
I saw a man.
The man is dying. The man is dying.
Is this the man, Sky?
Yes, yes.
This man is dying. This man is dying.
Die, must die, he is dying.
Lan, Sky is showing symptoms.
Confirmed that the victim is really Tali.
They are attacking the target. Go, Sergeant.
Yes, sir.
Oh shit, what should I do?
Fah.
The police are coming soon.
- Shit.
- Hurry up, fuck it.
- Oh my god!
- Stop.
Freeze!
Don't move!
- Don't move.
- Run away.
Fast!
Fah, run!
- Keng!
- Don't shoot!
Run away
I'm sorry, Keng.
I'm sorry.
What you said is that
Sky saw the picture in 'here'.
What is that?
That's right, what you said was that Sky would know
that Fah was going to kidnap Tali?
Oh, well.
Aren't you wondering why every time Fah kills someone,
Sky has such symptoms
and she can also knit the yarn as if she is in the scene.
I was also wondering about it.
Then I found the program on YouTube.
It's a supernatural mystery show, and there's footage of it.
It's footage about twins' minds communicating.
What's really interesting is that some pairs of twins
are raised separately and didn't know they had a twin.
But in the end, they share some events in life
that are coincidentally similar.
They call it Twin Soul.
Twin Soul?
Yes.
Let me give you an example.
There is a case of foreign children
who were raised separately
in different corners of a very large castle, but in the end, they were able to communicate with each other.
Does this mean that Sky can feel Fah's mind?
As far as I have observed,
Sky will only know when Fah kills someone.
Sky will see it in here.
Sky is an autistic child, so she can't explain
what she's seeing in her head.
Does Fah know what Sky is thinking?
One dead,
Another one was not caught.
It's no good.
- Who is the murderer who died?
- Yes, sir.
Keng,
Karan Homdrun.
Oh, the population register said he had killer genes,
but the test results from the body said otherwise.
It means that he sold his genes to other people.
See, sergeant.
I think this hot potato has fallen into your father's hands.
Never mind, your father is smart. He'll get through it.
What interests me more is
how would you answer reporters' questions?
Why did you have to use
such a famous star as the bait?
Don't you know that people are
already interested in this case?
Why did you have to make such a scene?
Because Tali was the victim that
the murderer wanted to kill.
Yeah, I know.
Then why didn't you let the undercover police go instead?
If something really happens to him,
can you take responsibility for it?
- Well, then it's fake, sir.
- Don't talk back to me.
Your job now is to catch the criminal.
And don't let anyone else die.
Yes, sir.
Oh, then
How is that actor doing now?
Isn't he being attacked by mobs?
I'd like to interview you. Please let us interview.
How are you, Tali?
How are you? Last night was a big deal.
Were you injured in any way?
Oh, everything is much better now. And then...
I would like to thank the police team
for taking such good care of me.
Otherwise, I would have been killed.
Really, I have to thank the police very much,
they took such good care of Ta.
If there's anything I can help you with, please tell me.
You can also tell Ta. I'm happy and willing to do so.
The killer will only choose victims who have killer genes.
So, does Tali also have the killer gene?
Yes, I do.
I have killer genes.
And now, all of my matters are under the care of the police.
I was wrong, so I have to accept the mistake.
In reality, Ta doesn't know anything about it.
It was me who did it.
The one who is at fault is me.
It's okay, mom.
Just imagine if one day your
child was branded as a murderer,
even though he just opened his eyes to the world.
As a mother, how would I accept this?
He has done good deeds and done great things for others.
Is this the kind of person
who is going to get up and kill people?
It is a killer gene law that is still being revised.
What is up with this law?
It's not fair at all.
Let me ask you this honestly.
Can good and evil really be determined by genes?
It's okay, Mom.
Sir,
the party has invited you to attend a meeting urgently.
If it's not convenient for you,
I'll let you know and postpone it.
I'm going today.
Sooner or later,
I have to go anyway.
We'll finally find out,
when I am no longer useful,
what are they going to do to me?
What's up?
The backlash, sis.
Instead of people criticizing
Tali for faking the killer genes,
it turned into sympathy and then admiration.
Isn't it good to end that way?
Who said that?
The person who got attacked instead is...
Dr. Chonlathorn.
Well, it's Tali's fan club.
They really cursed him.
I'm Dr. Chonlathorn Traikanon,
Prime Ministerial Candidates,
on behalf of the Palang Pracha Thai Progressive Party
I feel sorry for the serial murders that happened.
I would like to express my condolences
to those who lost loved ones.
Including parents,
all the relatives of those who lost loved ones.
Many people may be focusing on the issue
of the Genetic Killer Act.
I was the one who pushed for and enforced this law.
I still insist that what I did was for society's safety.
The situation over the past twenty years,
we can see that our society is peaceful.
There have been no serious cases.
Everyone can stay at home with warmth.
Until this unavoidable incident occurred.
Which is why I
cannot be certain that
this may be just a political discrediting move.
Or is there anyone
behind this murder case.
In my pure intentions,
I may have been distorted by a group of people.
And it is accused of being degrading
and obstructing humanity. Therefore,
to take full responsibility
I would like to resign as party leader
and prime ministerial candidate
from today onwards.
Everything you've done is for this, right, Fah?
We did it, Keng.
We knocked that damn Dr. down.
What a shame, Keng,
that you aren't standing beside us
and not seeing it before your own eyes.
It's because of me.
I made him die.
If he hadn't come back and saved me,
he probably wouldn't have died.
Fah.
It's not your fault, Fah.
It's not my fault either.
And it's not Keng's fault either.
It's those damn bastards' fault.
Those low-life bastards are oppressing us.
They make us stand up and fight like a dog that's been nailed to the head.
Now it's my mom's and my turn.
I need to settle my avenge with that low-life bastard.
After you announced your withdrawal,
the mob then dispersed.
Good.
It's better if they have gone away. They were annoying.
By the way, Pitak.
Once all those brainless people go back,
Tell the guards to leave as well.
I want to be alone and quiet.
okay
What's up?
I'm telling you the truth.
I don't really agree with you resigning
from Prime Ministerial candidate.
Election day is just a few days away.
Even though your popularity has dropped,
you may not get a majority,
but in any case, you still have
the right to enter the council.
Even though I am no longer a prime ministerial candidate,
my name is still on the party list.
Don't forget,
I won't give up on this easily.
It wasn't easy for me to push it into law, you know that.
Therefore,
I will never let anyone mess with it.
What are you going to do with the murderer?
What do you want me to do?
I'm not a policeman.
Actually, it was just a woman who went out to kill people,
then manipulated people in society to hate you.
Do something wrong and blame the law.
Saying that this law is incorrect, is that right?
It does look like
you're suffering more than me.
Thank you.
Go take a break.
We still have a lot of work to do.
If we include the star who was not killed
successfully, then that's ten.
Why is there still evidence?
But I really wonder why the sky
had to kill ten people. Why ten?
What does it mean? I don't understand.
Or just to match this song?
I'm guessing.
We think that Fah wants to oppose
the law to control killer genes.
If you guess so,
Fah has already eliminated Dr. Chonlathorn from becoming Prime Minister.
No, but she wants to cancel the law.
Or maybe it was because the tenth corpse was not killed,
so another corpse had to be killed.
I don't think that's it.
The yarn was in the killer's bag
and fell next to the victim
from the beginning.
I think the murderer has no way
of knowing that it will fail.
This also means that the game is not over yet.
What else does Fah want?
Oh, where are you going, Lan?
Go find someone to decode it.
- Wait for us.
Wait a minute.
I'm going too.
Runes
or runic letters,
in the native language, it is called fulltark.
These letters are old German
and mean secret or mysterious sound.
These letters are related to magic.
Started in Southern Europe
But it was widespread among the Germanic tribes and had 24 letters in total.
Each letter has its own meaning.
Sky Here's a rune comparison table.
It's okay. Sky can read it now.
So what's the riddle, Sky?
Ten slash ten.
Watch yourself.
What is it, Sky?
It means to watch out for yourself.
Who did the murderer say this to?
Fah, this doesn't mean Sky, right, son?
No, it's not.
If Fah was going to do something,
she would have done it since the day she invaded.
Oh,
excuse me.
Oh, Ms. Pang.
What's up?
The dough doesn't work well with the workpiece.
-I'd like to give you a gift. Please take a look.
-Oh, okay.
Oh
Is this it?
We'll have to connect them first.
Jigsaw.
Yes, yes, jigsaw puzzle.
Jigsaw
Yarn is a jigsaw puzzle.
What is a jigsaw puzzle? Sky
We need to carry the silk sheets together.
The answer may be here. The answer is here.
So how do we connect it, Sky?
Are you going to arrange them in order?
Uh-huh
Let's do it this way.
Start by sorting the bodies by the number of people killed.
First Corpse, Noppachai.
Noppachai, Nattha, Isriya, continue sorting.
You take it.
Isriya,
Anon,
Phra Phongsak,
Rapeephan, Pramthongtha,
Ornchuma,
Pakin,
and Tali.
We arrange them as 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10.
How about this?
This is not it.
Then let's sort
these two
three
What should we do, Sky?
It's still not right.
Or what? Should we do a long line?
It's ten long.
Give it a try.
One Noppachai, One Red
One, two, three, this one.
Ten, this one is nine.
Four Anon,
Four Anon.
Did your mom beat you again?
I'll treat your wound.
What kind of future doctor is this?
Even a wound like this, you can't even treat it right.
Let me see the wound.
Come on.
Let me see.
Is there anywhere else?
No more
Don't you dare lie to me.
I'll do it.
Your hands must be as long as Mae Nak's
to care for it yourself.
Let me see, come on.
Wow!
This time, your mom hit you quite hard.
Does it hurt?
Ouch!
Damn liar, you said it didn't hurt.
You are not being gentle.
Who is singing?
No one, Sky.
Yes, someone was singing. Sky really heard it.
What is this? Don't cling on to me.
Sky suddenly said that she heard someone singing.
Is this a ghost?
Oh you, you're working with corpses,
are you afraid of ghosts?
Corpses and ghosts are the same, sis.
Sky,
the song that you are hearing,
is this from here?
Yes.
The sound comes from here.
You have to sort according to the song.
Arranged by song, number one,
believe in your religion, Phra Phongsak.
Two, be traditional.
Three, listen to your parents and teachers.
Four, your words must be polite and gentle.
Five, must show gratitude.
Six, be sure to love working.
Seven, must study hard to become an expert.
Eight knows how to save money.
Nine, must be honest at all times.
Brave with sportsmanship.
And then ten.
Ten, make yourself useful.
It's not like this.
Not like this.
Start over with the fourth one.
Arranged in three rows. Arranged in three rows.
Then there will be some leftovers, Sky.
That's just right.
Let's start with the fourth one.
Start with the fourth sheet and then arrange it in threes.
Start with four and line up three in a row.
This is not the first sheet.
The first sheet is this one.
Asking for rice in the morning,
barefoot walking to collect alms, that is, a monk.
She is really a genius.
So what now,
who does Fah want to kill, Sky?
You have to turn it inside out. You have to turn it inside out.
P. Trikanont
Sky, does Fah want to kill me?
Why Lan?
What did you have against Fa?
Oh, Sergeant.
I first met her with you.
Is she really going to kill you?
I think
It would be better if she wanted to kill me
so that other people wouldn't have to suffer.
But I just wonder,
What message does Fah want to imply if she wants to kill me?
Sir,
The external camera system is ready.
We try it with a switch control car
and we can see every camera from every angle.
Why do you need to install cameras all over your house?
Isn't it not enough if we just wait to arrest them, Inspector?
We need evidence to incriminate Fa.
Don't forget that every time Fah causes trouble,
Fah always wears a mask.
But we have DNA, don't we, Inspector?
DNA is a big problem.
Because we cannot identify at all that
which DNA is Fah's? Which is Sky's?
This leaves us with no evidence to arrest Fah.
Then how can you be sure that Fah will come?
Sir, policeman.
Are you really going to meet my twin?
That's right.
Why, Sky? Are you scared?
My twin is very smart.
Sky is afraid that the twin will hurt you.
Sky.
I'm a policeman.
You know how to deal with bad guys well.
As for Sky, please stay in the house.
You must not go out at all, understand?
Sky has to stay in the house.
Don't worry, Sky.
Then I'll hurry back and prepare the decoding method with Teacher Sky again.
Is that okay?
Please wait a moment.
Could you please give me your hand, Officer?
um
What is this, Sky?
Algiz.
This rune symbolizes the elk.
Represents protection and guardian.
It also acts as a shield to protect against various evils.
It will help protect Sky's disciples.
In that case, can I have the other side too?
Thank you, Sky.
Fah, I know that Officer's home address.
I'll send you the location.
Fah.
Fah, why did you come back?
Why did you come back?
Why didn't you hurry up and run away?
You hurry up and go away.
The police will arrest me and your mother.
So that's it?
You're only worried about yourself and my mother
You've never been worried about me, have you?
Who taught you to go around killing people like this?
Where did you get such evil thoughts?
Why are you so cruel and inhumane, Fah?
Fah, where are you going?
Fah, Fah comes to see mommy.
Fah.
Mom, please go with me.
Fah, what are you going to do?
I will take my mother with me.
Take me with you.
Where are you taking your mother?
Just you alone, you can barely escape from the police.
Why are you dragging your mother into this mess?
Who said I would run away?
I will take you to kill that low-life bastard myself.
Low-life bastard!
Will you take me to that jerk?
Go, go, go.
No, no, no, no. This is too much, Fah.
If you're going to do evil, do it alone.
Don't drag your mom into this too.
Words are bad and evil.
I will go all the way to hell as you please.
Fah!
Fah, don't.
Grandma, don't stop us.
Don't do this, Fah.
I have to take my mother to kill him.
Let go!
-Fah.
- Let go.
I'm begging you.
Don't do this again.
Forgive them.
Let's not hold grudges against each other anymore.
Forgive?
Grandma, you dare say to forgive?
I am conceived from rape.
You still dare ask me to forgive that low-life bastard who raped Mom, Grandma?
I'm sorry.
If you're sorry,
go apologize to grandpa.
Because of you, grandpa had to die!
Let's go, Mom.
Fah, don't do this, dear.
Open the door.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
Fah.
Bancha,
I'm sorry you had to die.
A little bit more!
A little push!
Push. Push the baby.
Just a little bit more, honey.
Breathe, baby, breathe.
Push again
Duang, our grandchild is born already,
right? Is it a boy or a girl?
Duang, boy or girl?
Are you hard of hearing?
Boy or girl?
Throw it away
Hey, what do you mean?
Are you going to keep this child, this damn child,
to reinforce to our daughter
that she is pregnant without a father?
Do you want other people
to know that your child was raped?
But this is our grandchild, Grandma Duang.
I don't see it as my grandchild.
Hurry up and throw it away.
Make sure no one can see it.
Grandma Duang.
Can you hurry up?
- Let's go.
- Yeah, yeah.
Mom, I have a stomachache.
The baby is out now.
Why do you still have a stomachache?
Twin?
Officer, there's a child here.
Bancha,
I'm sorry I caused you to die.
May the Officer be safe. May Officer be safe.
- May the Officer be safe.
- What is Sky writing?
I see you've been writing for a long time.
Be safe.
May the Officer be safe.
What is it?
It's a runic symbol.
They believe that it will protect you from all dangers.
Sky,
Lan will be fine. Everyone is prepared.
Sky, don't worry.
All units are prepared
If I don't order, don't come in.
I insist that I want to capture her alive.
I'm leaving now.
Officer.
What else, Sky?
Sky, are you going to write another amulet for me?
Officer, please don't kill Miss Fah,
Sky's twin sister?
Fah.
Where are you taking me, dear?
Where are you taking me?
Mom is tired now.
Fah.
I'm tired. Where are we going?
Fah. I told you I'm tired. Where are you taking me?
Hold on a little longer, Mom. We're almost there.
What's your problem?
I'll take you to see this guy.
Let go, let me go.
That low-life bastard!
Where is he?
Where is he? I will kill him.
Where is he? Tell me.
I'll kill him. Where is he? I'll kill him.
How is Sky?
Lan, Sky hasn't shown any symptoms yet.
How are things over there?
It's fine.
Fah isn't here yet.
Then do as Lan said.
Okay.
All units, change orders.
Cancel the mission.
Ouch!
Must die.
What's up, Sky?
Lan, Sky is showing symptoms. Lan, be careful.
Noted. That's all.
All units, change orders, get ready.
The killer is coming.
Must die, about to die
Sky, Sky.
Sky, calm down, Sky.
Sky, come on, listen.
Is Fah with Lan now?
Fah is with the victim, right?
Found him.
Found the victim.
Sky, I haven't seen Fah come at all.
Sky said that Fah had found you.
Sky, Fah really met Lan, right?
The victim is not the Officer.
How can it not be, Sky?
Lan.
Sky said the victim was not you.
So who is the victim?
Sky, Sky. What do you see in your head? Who, Sky?
Sky often sees this person on TV.
Who, Sky?
People who appear on TV often
Sky doesn't know his name.
Sky doesn't know the name.
Lan, Lan.
Does Lan have any other family members
whose names start with P?
No, there aren't any.
Or it's him.